lush gardens delicious cuisine statues
of fat cats these are all things I do
not think about when I think of Bangkok
I'll admit sex is foremost in my mind
now I'm all for ladies of the night but
it's not just about ladies here you
gotta hand it to Thailand by a
progressive when it comes to sex they
even recognize transgender people in
their constitution and people around the
world have heard of the Thai sex workers
known as lady voice ladyboys blur the
line between Western notions of drag and
trans lady boys live very openly in Thai
society so how exactly did Thailand
crack the code and become more
forward-thinking than we are armed in
Bangkok to do extensive research in the
name of LGBTQ rights and I tip
generously so I can sit down with three
ladies and an interpreter to learn more
you never hide that your lady boys you
never you always very open about this I
love my penis so I would say I have a
penis who still has their penis I'm
gonna say yes I have the penis you have
a penis you have a penis you no longer
have the penis where did the chub
come from the man come to
Thailand they don't know she was he so
to take up to the room and then after
takeoff is it holy lady but boy all
about the previs so in Thailand they
call themselves alcea which means like a
boning Queen a woman who can actually
top girl
many people in America would say this is
not very moral work what would you say
to them I'm not rubbing anyone I'm not
killing anyone
I'm not causing anyone any trouble so
why would you say that as for them it's
like they're it comes from their own
will their own will that they want to be
your direct straight look I feel like
you're living the best of both worlds
you get to dress in flashy clothing and
you get to stand up having a piece but
they prefer to use the ladies room be
tuned I wanna sit down wait now I must
admit before meeting these ladies my
main source of information about Bangkok
were movies that took place in Bangkok
and this is it Bangkok goodtime city you
in Bangkok sweetie this reason they
don't call them Bank on
and maybe all these cartoonish versions
distract everyone from learning even the
most basic facts about real lady boys do
you consider yourself transgender yeah
does the government recognize all your
rights Yong Yong Lau they already accept
them in the 6th street they was telling
her that her paperwork is not qualified
for them prefer a guy who looks like a
guy I see so the government is tolerant
of trans people as long as they stick to
one job and that can lead to a very
extreme choice transitioning becomes a
financial decision because they have no
other way to make money she says some
people cut it off not because they're
generally wanted but for work do you
experience our bigotry from the from the
general public in Thailand active person
is still auntie I had this all wrong so
I sat down with a Thai LGBTQ activist to
learn more
the term is that offensive a
little bit because people how does they
understood that is someone who
are we attached with the industry
because generally people talk about this
group of people as the term transgender
do you think the sex industry gives
Thailand a bad name
a little bit that's why feminists try to
eliminate the image of Thailand is the
sexxxy because it's a beautiful country
the food's amazing but whether the first
thought that I have when I think of
Bangkok is the the club now sure these
three ladies seem to enjoy their jobs
and they told me some dirty not
for basic cable stories but they at
least deserve some other options for
work even in the West progress can be
slow but as more countries make strides
on LGBTQ rights
guess who's starting to feel the
trickle-down effect do the clients
mostly prefer you to have penises or not
this is quite a new trend people want to
try with the penis when
see the dick may like run into them like
they like a lady spaceship so the penis
is in fashion right now yeah that's
right
the penis is in fashion before the the
girls were cutting them off but now most
of the men want the penis to be there is
that progress that is a procare's
because if they have the body in which
this do you have there already no sexual
organ and they feel free to to do
everything that they like they confirm
who they are exactly it's 2019 for
sake just accept these ladies for
who they are but it did Donna me that
there was one topic we hadn't discussed
how common is it for women that want to
be men in this country when she's saying
that there's lady boys who also date the
lesbian all right so the lady boys you
want to be with women women who wants to
become man right like a lesbian who will
also date who still have dates
wife is complicated you can say that
again
[Music]